ILR School Fiscal Office Files /4010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Fiscal Office Files
1946-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4010
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Collection of ILR School Fiscal Office files including: catalogues, inventories, fiscal records, purchase vouchers, work orders, requisitions and correspondence, etc.
3082808
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4047: ILR School Fiscal Office Additional Records /4122: ILR School Fiscal Office Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3082808
- Office Equipment Catalogues and Inventories, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Travel Expense 4000, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Expense Accounts 2000-, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Travel Vouchers, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Expense Accounts, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Expense Accounts3 6000, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Vouchers 1-1200, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ILR School Archives Fiscal Records, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ILR School Archives Fiscal Records, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Purchase Vouchers 600-699, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Purchase Vouchers 500-599, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Purchase Vouchers 400-499, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Purchase Vouchers 300-399, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Purchase Vouchers 201-300, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Purchase Vouchers 101-200, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Purchase Vouchers 1-100, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- College Stores Bills, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Work Orders, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Purchase Vouchers 1400-1499, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Purchase Vouchers 1300-1399, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Purchases Vouchers 1200-1299, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Purchase Vouchers 1100-1199, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Purchase Vouchers 1000-1099, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Purchase Vouchers 601-700 800-900, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Purchase Vouchers 501-600, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Purchase Vouchers, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Purchase Vouchers 300-400, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Purchase Vouchers 101-200, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Work Orders, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Requisitions 800-899, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Requisitions 700-799, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Requisitions 600-699, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Requisitions 500-599, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Requisitions 1500-1599, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Requisitions 1400-1499, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Requisitions 1300-1399, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Requisitions 1100-1199, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Requisitions 1000-1099, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Requisitions 900-999, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Budget, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Credits to College Funds, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Salaries - Payroll, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Work Orders, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Samples Printing, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Cornell Co-Operative Society, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Memorandum, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Cornell Co-operative Society, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Albany Publicity Service, Inc. NYSSILR, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Memorandum, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Memorandum, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Memorandum, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Pertinent Documents and Correspondence, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 501-8602 (Huttar) Job and Economic Conference, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 506-8301 Critical Issues in ILR - Srb., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 509-8100 (Nash) NYS Credit and Cert. Pr., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 509-8300 (Harrison) NYS Continuity of EMP., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 509-8638 (L. Gray) Worker Exchange Program, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 509-8641 (Ray Smith) NYC Training Project, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 509-8644 Conf.-NYS Education Network for Working Women, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- 509-8645 (Wasmuth) Rehab Training, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 509-8646 (L. Gray) Puerto Rican Leadership, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 509-8647 (Wertheimer) Ford-Women's Studies, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 509-8648 (L. Gray) USDL Regional Manpower Institute, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 509-8649 (L. Gray) Puerto Rican Leadership, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 509-8651 (Pivetz) win Project Buffalo (New York State-Dol), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 509-8652 (649) Invisible Women (Wertheimer), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- 509-8653 (LALL) Low Income Health-NYS, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 509-8654 (Wasmuth) Teaching Grant Rehab. Admin. - Hew, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- 509-8655 (Wasmuth) Short-Term Rehab. Training-Hew, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- 509-8656 (LALL) Occ. Safety and Health, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- 509-8657 (Wertheimer) Carnegie Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- 509-8658 (Harrison) Educational Services with Albany N.Y., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 515-8301 (Miller) Planning and Compilation of a Thesaurus, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- 521-8301 Liberian Codification (Konvitz) (313), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- 521-8302 Amer. Arbitration. Assn. (331) (McKelvey/Yaffe), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- 521-8309 (Kochan) Imp. Of Compulsory. Arb. On Police and Firefighters, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- 521-8310 (Cullen) Construction Industry USDL J-9-P-5-0107, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- 521-8311 Cullen/McCabe Railroad Manpower Adj. USDL 91-36-76-04, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 521-8312 (Finch) Labor History 76-5-07, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 521-8600 (Neufeld) Philip Taft Labor History Award, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 522-8303 (515) OFCC conference (Hildebrand/R. Smith), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 522-8306 (Hildebrand/Block) USDL 91-36-76-33 Doc. Dissertation, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 522-8307 (Dillingham) Risk and Wage Different. USDL J-9-F-6-0087, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 522-8310 (Hutchens) NYS Welfare Benefits, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 522-8311 (R. Smith) OFCC Mgt. Conf. Planning, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 522-8314 (Dyer/Smith) OFCC conf. J-9-E-7-0147, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 525-8335 (Whyte) Employee Participation in Ownership and Management, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 525-8337 Eval. Of NYS Alcohol Consultation, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 525-8338 (Whyte) Career Research, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 525-8339 (Trice) Alcoholism Policy Data, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- 525-8341 (Whyte) Strengthen Local Economies USDL 91-36-76-39, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- 525-8340 Eval. Of NYS Alcohol Consultation Trice, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- 525-8344 (Whyte) New Systems of Work and Participation MH 29259-01, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- 525-8345 (Trice) Eval. NYS OCC Alcoh cons, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- 525-8346 NYS-Chap, (Trice), 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- 525-8900 (Bacharach/Reader) Reader Fellowship H-2621-RG, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- 526-8300 (Foltman) NYS Continuity of Emp., 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- 526-8301 (Risley) Personnel Rules Handbook, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- 526-8304 (Risley) Personnel Rules Handbook, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 23)